http://www.deeter.com/privacy/

Access to Our Website
Deeter Foundry is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website. You are free to access and browse our site without disclosing personal data, and you can be assured that we endeavor to protect the confidentiality and security of your information at all times. We do not release any information to outside parties without the express permission of our website users.
Information Collection
Deeter Foundry does not automatically collect personal information from our website nor do we use cookies to store personal information. We do not link personal information about specific individuals with any other information we collect, either on our website or in our facilities. We do not collect personal information from other sources such as public records or private databases nor do we release or sell personal information about those who access our website. We do collect personal information that is voluntarily provided while using our services. All privacy practices and regulations apply to this information, as well.
Confidentiality and Security
Deeter Foundry does not disclose personal information to other organizations. We ensure that personal information will not be disclosed to federal or state institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation. We have instituted technical measures to protect personal information in our files from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All Deeter Foundry employees who have access to and who process personal information are obligated to maintain the confidentiality of the information. Our website does provide access to additional information with links to other sites. It is our hope that these sites offer privacy protection, but Deeter Foundry is not responsible for their content or privacy practices.
Deeter Foundry
Legal
Privacy
Sitemap
About Us
Contact Us
Delivery
Distribution Yards
Deeter Foundry | P.O. Box 29708 | Lincoln, NE 68529 | p:
800.234.7466 | Legal | Privacy | Sitemap
